http://thediscountsextoys.com/policies/privacy-policy

Search
close (esc)
Privacy Protection
Your privacy is of the utmost importance to us. It is your right to know the terms and conditions surrounding the use of your personal information on our website.
When you place an order, we will ask you for your name, email address, mailing address and phone number. This information is only for the billing and shipping process. We will email you an order confirmation and a tracking number once the order is complete. We’ll never call you, we will return your call only if you call us.
If we need to contact you, it will be via email. To assure proper communication, please be sure that the email address you supply is valid in the case that we need to contact you regarding your order.
Discreet Billing
Your credit card statement for your purchases with Adultys site will read "AST Inc." Your purchases are completely safe, secure, private and confidential as it should be when ordering personal products.
100% Guarantee
Customer satisfaction in every sense of the term is our highest goal. We back each purchase with a satisfaction guarantee and refund policy. If you are dissatisfied for any reason with the item you ordered at Adultys site, you may request a refund within 15 days of purchasing the product.
Plain Packaging
Your package ships discreetly in a plain box with "AST Inc." as the return sender. It looks just like any other package, but secretly contains your items.
How We Protect Your Privacy
Your privacy and confidentiality are our top priority, and we've made it the cornerstone of our business. We never sell, trade or rent your personal information to any third parties under any circumstances. We value your trust very highly, and will work to protect the security and privacy of any personal information you provide to us and will only use it as we have described in our Privacy Policy.
Safe Shopping at  Adultys site, We want you to know that you are completely secure when ordering from Adultys site. We use a technology called Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), which encrypts (or encodes) sensitive  information before it is sent over the Internet.
More about Privacy
Privacy Policy
Your credit card is processed immediately, we do not store credit card numbers when entered. You will know immediately if your transaction was declined or approved, after processing, you will be shown an order number, please print or save this  receipt for your records.
Your personal information is never sold, rented or released to any third party that is not involved in the transaction and delivery process. We do NOT send flyers, promotional offers or newsletters to your mailing address or to your e-mail address, unless you will ask for it by Subscription.
Your credit card is billed by "AST Inc." for your privacy.
Your Security - How We Protect You
When you place an order online, your personal information and credit card information are encrypted using high-grade up to 256-bit SSL encryption before being sent over the internet. SSL encryption is a method by which information transmitted across the Internet is scrambled to the point where it's indecipherable by anyone who should intercept the data before it reaches it's destination.
256-bit encryption is an upgrade from the standard and widely used 128-bit encryption. We use 256-bit because we understand the importance of protecting your identity, your personal information and your credit card information.
We have upgraded our online checkout process to be as secure as possible by implementing the most up-to-date methods as required by merchants from the credit card processing company - we have even exceeded their minimum security requirements to protect your information better. Your credit card is processed immediately, we do not store credit card numbers.
When shopping with us, submitting your information over the internet is as secure as possible, so have peace of mind knowing that we, here at The Discount Sex Toys.com, take the protection of your privacy, personal information and your identity extremely seriously.
Payment
All prices are in U.S. Dollars. We accept all credit cards, Visa, MasterCard, Discover, American Express, PayPal and More. Your credit card statement will be billed by AST Inc. for your privacy.
Shipping
We ship to USA, Canada, and military bases.
Orders normally ship the same day or next business day after being placed.
Please note that overnight and 3-day orders get priority and if all the items are in stock, these orders will always ship the same day or next business day.
Standard ground orders usually ship the same day or the next business day.
** Please note: Processing time and shipping time excludes weekends and statutory holidays when our warehouse and the mail carriers are closed.
We use plain brown boxes with no reference to the contents, it is discreet for your privacy. Only a return address and the shipping address is on the shipping label, there is no company name listed. The packing list is located inside the box with a list of the products that are in the order. Our shipping method is very discreet, not even the delivery person will know what is inside the box.
We ship with USPS, FedEx or UPS.
Our warehouse will chose the best shipping option:
** We strongly suggest a physical address (not a P.O. box number) for orders of higher value so that the package can be signed for upon delivery.
Your box gets shipped by USPS, FedEx or UPS, you will receive an email with a tracking number once your package has left the warehouse. With this, you will be able to view the progress of your package by entering the tracking number at usps.com, FedEx.com or UPS.com.
After a few days, if you have not received a tracking number, please email our customer service center (info@adultys.com) and we will promptly reply with your tracking number.
International Shipping to:
We are not liable for import charges, tariffs or customs duties for packages.
We are not liable for items seized by customs officers.
You may be charged customs duties upon delivery, please be aware of this.
Your order total will be charged in US Dollars to your credit card, please be aware that exchange rates from US Dollars to Canadian Dollars will apply to your charge, to be determined by the current exchange rate.
Please note that orders may take up to 2 weeks to be delivered as packages must wait for customs clearance.
Other
Sometimes, manufacturers change the packaging, the color or the design of an item. The items you receive may not appear exactly the same as pictured on the website. In some cases, substitutions may be made. We reserve the right to limit quantities and refuse and order.
Choosing a selection results in a full page refresh.
Press the space key then arrow keys to make a selection.
